Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2009 and undated, (2399 volumes)
  - Dungeons and Dragons
    - Character Sheets. Published by no place: Wizards of the Coast, undated., D03791793$ (Box BG 39, Volume 55)
    - Conversion Manual. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, undated., D03791794/ (Box BG 39, Volume 57)
    - Deluxe Character Sheets. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, undated., D04382060N (Box BG 39, Volume 89)
    - Deluxe Dungeon Master's Screen. Published by no place: Wizards of the Coast, undated., D03791795+ (Box BG 39, Volume 66)
    - Dungeon Master Screen. Published by no place: Wizards of the Coast, undated., D03791792 (Box BG 39, Volume 54)
    - Gazetteer. Published by no place: Wizards of the Coast, undated., D04382058U (Box BG 39, Volume 84)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Kara-Tur Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., undated., D04382061O (Box BG 39, Volume 90)
  - Earthdawn
    - Earthdawn: The Age of Legend, Hardcover. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04403714N (Box BG 39, Volume 1595)
    - GameMaster Pack. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Mists of Betrayal. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1993., D04382692Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1381)
    - Creatures of Barsaive. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382678 (Box BG 39, Volume 1372)
    - Denizens of Earthdawn: Volume 1. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382695. (Box BG 39, Volume 1376)
    - Denizens of Earthdawn: Volume 2. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382700O (Box BG 39, Volume 1375)
    - Earthdawn. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04383048U (Box BG 39, Volume 1409)
    - Earthdawn Companion. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382691X (Box BG 39, Volume 1382)
    - Earthdawn: The Age of Legend, Paperback. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04403720K (Box BG 39, Volume 1617)
    - Infected. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382694- (Box BG 39, Volume 1379)
    - Parlainth Adventures. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382702Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1378)
    - Shattered Pattern. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382701P (Box BG 39, Volume 1377)
    - Terror in the Skies. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1994., D04382693Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1380)
    - Blades. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04383044Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1395)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 5. Published by Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications, 1995., D04403792T (Box BG 39, Volume 1609)
    - Horrors. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04382698/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1374)
    - Legends of Earthdawn. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04382699+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1373)
    - Sky Point Adventures. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04383045R (Box BG 39, Volume 1396)
    - The Adept's Way. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1995., D04382711Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1371)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 6. Published by Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications, 1996., D04403791S (Box BG 39, Volume 1608)
    - Magic: A Manual of Mystic Secrets. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04382668. (Box BG 39, Volume 1394)
    - Prelude to War. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04383055S (Box BG 39, Volume 1401)
    - The Book of Exploration. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04383046S (Box BG 39, Volume 1397)
    - The Earthdawn Survival Guide. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04383058V (Box BG 39, Volume 1399)
    - The Serpent River. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04383047T (Box BG 39, Volume 1398)
    - Throal Adventures. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04383059W (Box BG 39, Volume 1400)
    - Throal: The Dwarf Kingdom. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1996., D04383054R (Box BG 39, Volume 1403)
    - Arcane Mysteris of Barsaive. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04383052P (Box BG 39, Volume 1405)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 8. Published by Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications, 1997., D04403790R (Box BG 39, Volume 1607)
    - Earthdawn Journal, Vol. 9. Published by Cedar Rapids, IA: Sword of the Knight Publications, 1997., D04403789Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1606)
    - The Blood Wood. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04383056T (Box BG 39, Volume 1402)
    - The Secret Societies of Barsaive. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04383050N (Box BG 39, Volume 1407)
    - The Theran Empire. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1997., D04383051O (Box BG 39, Volume 1406)
    - Crystal Raiders of Barsaive. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04383049V (Box BG 39, Volume 1408)
    - The Ork Nation of Cara Fahd. Published by Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation, 1998., D04383053Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1404)
  - Element Masters
    - Player's Manual, 1st ed.. Published by Virginia Beach, VA: Escape Ventures, 1982., D04403851P (Box BG 39, Volume 1670)
    - The First Border Patrol. Published by Virginia Beach, VA: Escape Ventures, 1982., D04403852Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1671)
  - Elfquest
    - Elfquest: The Official Roleplaying Game, 2nd edition. Published by Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1989., D03804364S (Box BG 39, Volume 382)
  - Elric!
    - Elric. Published by Albany, CA: The Chaosium, 1977., D04405648V (Box BG 39, Volume M4)
    - Elric! Dark Fantasy Roleplaying Game. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1993., D03804341N (Box BG 39, Volume 256)
    - Melnibone: Dragon Isle and Dreaming City. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1993., D03804348U (Box BG 39, Volume 255)
    - Fate of Fools: Pawns of Destiny. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1994., D03804345R (Box BG 39, Volume 252)
    - The Bronze Grimoire: Magic and the Supernatural. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1994., D03804346S (Box BG 39, Volume 251)
    - The Unknown East: Forgotten Foes of the Bright Empire. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., 1995., D03804347T (Box BG 39, Volume 254)
    - Elric! Gamemaster Screen. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., undated., D04382122M (Box BG 39, Volume 253)
    - Atlas of the Young Kingdoms Vol. I: The Northern Continent. Published by Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc., undated., D03804344Q (Box BG 39, Volume 250)
  - Encyclopedia Harnica
    - Encyclopedia Harnica 4. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Publications, 1984., D04382901R (Box BG 39, Volume 1191)
    - Olokand, Atlas Harnica, and Manor. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1984., D04382900Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1190)
    - Cities of Harn. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1987., D04382904U (Box BG 39, Volume 1193)
    - Cities of Harn: Son of Cities. Published by Blaine, WA: Columbia Games, 1987., D04382903T (Box BG 39, Volume 1192)
  - Epxae Islands Mysteries
    - Stones of the Selt, 2nd ed. Published by Abilene, TX: Dragon Tree Press, 1981., D04403802L (Box BG 39, Volume 1627)
  - Espionage
    - Border Crossing. Published by San Mateo, CA: Hero Games, 1983., D04563849$ (Box BG 39, Volume 2117)
    - Stormhaven (#3301). Published by Scottsdale, AZ: Flying Buffalo, Inc., 1983., D04563915X (Box BG 39, Volume 2144)
  - Fading Suns
    - Fading Suns. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1995., D04382368Y (Box BG 39, Volume 741)
    - Byzantium Secundus. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1996., D03804359W (Box BG 39, Volume 721)
    - Forbidden Lore. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1996., D03804358V (Box BG 39, Volume 720)
    - Lords of the Known Worlds. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1996., D03804357U (Box BG 39, Volume 719)
    - Priests of the Celestial Sun. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1996., D04382349X (Box BG 39, Volume 717)
    - Weapon Compendium. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1996., D04382345T (Box BG 39, Volume 708)
    - Weird Places. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1996., D03804356T (Box BG 39, Volume 718)
    - Fading Suns: Player's Companion. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1997., D03574312P (Box BG 39, Volume 716)
    - Merchants of the Jumpweb. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1997., D03574310N (Box BG 39, Volume 714)
    - The Dark Between the Stars. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1997., D03574313Q (Box BG 39, Volume 715)
    - Children of the Gods: Obun and Ukar. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1998., D03574311O (Box BG 39, Volume 713)
    - Sinners and Saints. Published by Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc., 1998., D03574308U (Box BG 39, Volume 712)
  - Fantasy Hero
    - The Roleplaying Game of Epic Adventure: Fantasy Hero. Published by San Mateo, CA: Hero Games, 1984., D04563826Y (Box BG 39, Volume 2132)
    - Magic Items: A Magical Supplement (#29). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1987., D04563859/ (Box BG 39, Volume 2127)
    - The Spell Book (#41). Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1989., D04563805V (Box BG 39, Volume 2106)
    - Fantasy Hero Companion. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1990., D04564007Q (Box BG 39, Volume 2264)
    - Fantasy Hero Companion II. Published by Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises, 1992., D04564005O (Box BG 39, Volume 2262)
  - Fantasy Master
    - Aesheba: Greek Africa. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: New Infinities Productions, Inc., 1987., D04382725V (Box BG 39, Volume 1298)
  - Fiend Folio
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382439X (Box BG 39, Volume 811)
  - Flash Gordon
    - Flash Gordon and the Warriors of Mongo. Published by Roslyn, NY: Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1977., D04403862R (Box BG 39, Volume 1681)
  - Foreign Legion
    - Macta. Published by Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications, 1979., D04405650O (Box BG 39, Volume M5)
    - Moulay Ishmael. Published by Mission, KS: Bearhug Publications, 1979., D04405650O (Box BG 39, Volume M5)
  - Forgotten Realms
    - Moonshae. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1987., D04382095V (Box BG 39, Volume 200)
    - Under Illefarn. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1987., D04382105N (Box BG 39, Volume 212)
    - Waterdeep and the North. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1987., D04382096W (Box BG 39, Volume 201)
    - Dreams of the Red Wizard. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382091R (Box BG 39, Volume 196)
    - Empires of the Sands. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382094U (Box BG 39, Volume 199)
    - Lords of Darkness. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D03804385V (Box BG 39, Volume 353)
    - Mad Monkey vs. The Dragon Claw. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382109R (Box BG 39, Volume 216)
    - Ruins of Adventure. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04373272S (Box BG 39, Volume 211)
    - Swords of the Iron Legion. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382114N (Box BG 39, Volume 221)
    - The Magister. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382093T (Box BG 39, Volume 198)
    - The Savage Frontier. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382092S (Box BG 39, Volume 197)
    - The Throne of Bloodstone. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1988., D04382115O (Box BG 39, Volume 222)
    - Curse of the Azure Bonds. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04373271R (Box BG 39, Volume 210)
    - Gateway to Ravens Bluff, the Living City. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382113M (Box BG 39, Volume 220)
    - Hall of Heroes. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04373270Q (Box BG 39, Volume 195)
    - Kara-Tur Trail Map. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382157U (Box BG 39, Volume 391)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382440P (Box BG 39, Volume 812)
    - Shadowdale. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382104M (Box BG 39, Volume 209)
    - Tantras. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382103L (Box BG 39, Volume 208)
    - Test of the Samurai. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382107P (Box BG 39, Volume 214)
    - The Bloodstone Lands. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382090Q (Box BG 39, Volume 194)
    - The City of Waterdeep Trail Map. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382158V (Box BG 39, Volume 392)
    - Waterdeep. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1989., D04382102K (Box BG 39, Volume 207)
    - Adventures. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04373267W (Box BG 39, Volume 185)
    - Black Courser. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382150N (Box BG 39, Volume 355)
    - Blood Charge. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382149V (Box BG 39, Volume 354)
    - Draconomicon. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D03804387X (Box BG 39, Volume 351)
    - Dwarves Deep. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382088X (Box BG 39, Volume 192)
    - Halls of the High King. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382101J (Box BG 39, Volume 206)
    - Inside Ravens Bluff, the Living City. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382112L (Box BG 39, Volume 219)
    - Old Empires. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382089Y (Box BG 39, Volume 193)
    - Oriental Adventures: Ninja Wars. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382106O (Box BG 39, Volume 213)
    - Oriental Adventures: Ronin Challenge. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382108Q (Box BG 39, Volume 215)
    - Storm Riders. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D04382151O (Box BG 39, Volume 356)
    - The Forgotten Realms Atlas. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1990., D03804458W (Box BG 39, Volume 393)
    - Anauroch. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382087W (Box BG 39, Volume 190)
    - Endless Armies. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382153Q (Box BG 39, Volume 358)
    - Fires of Zatal. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382154R (Box BG 39, Volume 359)
    - Horde Campaign. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04373269Y (Box BG 39, Volume 191)
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382443S (Box BG 39, Volume 815)
    - Nightmare Keep. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382100I (Box BG 39, Volume 205)
    - Nightwatch in the Living City. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382111K (Box BG 39, Volume 218)
    - Ports of Ravens Bluff. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D04382110J (Box BG 39, Volume 217)
    - The Drow of the Underdark. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1991., D03804388Y (Box BG 39, Volume 350)
    - Aurora's Whole Realms Catalogue. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D03804457V (Box BG 39, Volume 390)
    - City of Gold. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382152P (Box BG 39, Volume 357)
    - Gold and Glory. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04373268X (Box BG 39, Volume 188)
    - Haunted Halls of Eveningstar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382099Z (Box BG 39, Volume 204)
    - Hordes of Dragonspear. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382098Y (Box BG 39, Volume 203)
    - Pirates of the Fallen Stars. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D03804390R (Box BG 39, Volume 349)
    - The Great Glacier. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D04382086V (Box BG 39, Volume 189)
    - Volo's Guide to Waterdeep. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1992., D03804459X (Box BG 39, Volume 389)
    - Doom of Daggerdale. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382097X (Box BG 39, Volume 202)
    - The Code of the Harpers. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D03804391S (Box BG 39, Volume 348)
    - The Dalelands. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382136R (Box BG 39, Volume 327)
    - The Jungles of Chult. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382084T (Box BG 39, Volume 186)
    - The Player's Guide to the Forgotten Realms Campaign. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D03804386W (Box BG 39, Volume 352)
    - The Shining South. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D04382085U (Box BG 39, Volume 187)
    - Volo's Guide to the North. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1993., D03804461Q (Box BG 39, Volume 386)
    - Book of Lairs. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D04382148U (Box BG 39, Volume 343)
    - Cormyr. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D04382119S (Box BG 39, Volume 229)
    - Elves of Evermeet. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D03804392T (Box BG 39, Volume 347)
    - Marco Volo Arrival. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D04382139U (Box BG 39, Volume 334)
    - Marco Volo Departure. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D04382141N (Box BG 39, Volume 336)
    - Marco Volo Journey. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D04382140M (Box BG 39, Volume 335)
    - Volo's Guide the the Sword Coast. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1994., D03804462R (Box BG 39, Volume 387)
    - Elminster's Ecologies Appendix I: The Battle of Bones, Hill of Lost Souls. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382138T (Box BG 39, Volume 329)
    - Elminster's Ecologies Appendix II: The High Moor, The Serpent Hills. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382137S (Box BG 39, Volume 328)
    - Giantcraft. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D03804395W (Box BG 39, Volume 345)
    - Pages from the Mages. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D03804397Y (Box BG 39, Volume 344)
    - The Moonsea. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382118R (Box BG 39, Volume 228)
    - The Return of Randal Morn. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382142O (Box BG 39, Volume 337)
    - The Secret of Spiderhaunt. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382143P (Box BG 39, Volume 338)
    - The Seven Sisters. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D03804393U (Box BG 39, Volume 346)
    - The Sword of the Dales. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D04382144Q (Box BG 39, Volume 339)
    - Volo's Guide to Cormyr. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D03804460P (Box BG 39, Volume 388)
    - Wizards and Rogues of the Realms. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1995., D03804398Z (Box BG 39, Volume 331)
    - Dungeon Crawl Undermountain Maddgoth's Castle. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D04382146S (Box BG 39, Volume 341)
    - Dungeon Crawl Undermountain Stardock. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D04382145R (Box BG 39, Volume 340)
    - Dungeon Crawl Undermountain The Lost Level. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D04382147T (Box BG 39, Volume 342)
    - Faiths and Avatars. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1996., D03804403M (Box BG 39, Volume 317)
    - Heroes' Lorebook. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D03804396X (Box BG 39, Volume 332)
    - How the Mighty are Fallen. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1996., D04382135Q (Box BG 39, Volume 326)
    - The Vilhon Reach: Usable by Characters of All Levels. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D04382117Q (Box BG 39, Volume 227)
    - Volo's Guide to All Things Magical. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D03804389Z (Box BG 39, Volume 333)
    - Volo's Guide to the Dalelands. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D03805875- (Box BG 39, Volume 385)
    - Warriors and Priests of the Realms. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1996., D03804394V (Box BG 39, Volume 330)
    - Castle Spulzeer. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1997., D04382133O (Box BG 39, Volume 321)
    - Four from Cormyr. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1997., D03804400J (Box BG 39, Volume 323)
    - Powers and Pantheons. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1997., D03805814T (Box BG 39, Volume 316)
    - Prayers from the Faithful. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1997., D03804401K (Box BG 39, Volume 322)
    - Calimport. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382120K (Box BG 39, Volume 226)
    - Cormanthyr: Empire of the Elves. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D03804399- (Box BG 39, Volume 324)
    - Cult of the Dragon. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D03804402L (Box BG 39, Volume 320)
    - Demihuman Deities. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D03804463S (Box BG 39, Volume 313)
    - Demihumans of the Realms. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D03805816V (Box BG 39, Volume 314)
    - For Duty and Deity. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382131M (Box BG 39, Volume 318)
    - Hellgate Keep. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382132N (Box BG 39, Volume 319)
    - Kidnapped. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382130L (Box BG 39, Volume 311)
    - The City of Ravens Bluff. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D03804464T (Box BG 39, Volume 312)
    - The Fall of Myth Drannor. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D04382134P (Box BG 39, Volume 325)
    - Villains' Lorebook, 1st edition. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1998., D03804465U (Box BG 39, Volume 310)
    - Drizzt Do'Urden's Guide to the Underdark. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D03804468X (Box BG 39, Volume 305)
    - Sea of Fallen Stars. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D03804467W (Box BG 39, Volume 307)
    - Skullport. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D03804466V (Box BG 39, Volume 308)
    - The Accursed Tower. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D04382129T (Box BG 39, Volume 309)
    - Wyrmskull Throne. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 1999., D03804469Y (Box BG 39, Volume 306)
    - Cloak and Dagger. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D03804404N (Box BG 39, Volume 303)
    - Pool of Radiance: Attack on Myth Drannor. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D03804405O (Box BG 39, Volume 302)
    - Secrets of the Magister. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D03805815U (Box BG 39, Volume 315)
    - The Dragon's Lair. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D03804406P (Box BG 39, Volume 301)
    - The Dungeon of Death. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D04382128S (Box BG 39, Volume 304)
    - Volo's Guide to Baldur's Gate II. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2000., D03804362Q (Box BG 39, Volume 384)
    - Dungeons and Dragons Campaign Setting: Forgotten Realms. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2001., D04373261Q (Box BG 39, Volume 179)
    - Lord of Darkness. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2001., D03804409S (Box BG 39, Volume 297)
    - Magic of Faerun. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2001., D03804408R (Box BG 39, Volume 298)
    - Monster Compendium: Monsters of Faerun. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2001., D03804407Q (Box BG 39, Volume 300)
    - City of the Spider Queen. Published by Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast, 2002., D03804411L (Box BG 39, Volume 296)